ATHM Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6524/003 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Arranged Alphabetically
  - E, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 11: Intachable irretrecissable solide, Emile roussel Marque deposee Roubaix., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Unimpeachable, unshrinkable, solid. Roubaix, France: Emile Roussel, n.d. Gold lettering and image of lion on very thin paper. 19 x 10 cm.
    - Item 12: Empire, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Image of Statue of Liberty in center. 20 x 23 cm.
    - Item 13: Empire AAA Padding, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering within green frame on white/cream background. 14.5 x 17 cm.
    - Item 14: Empire Shawl Hamilton Mill, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Style ______. N.p., n.d. Red and gold crown in center against cream background. 8.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 15: Empire State, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Excelsior. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering; image of two women in center, one holding anchor, one hold scales, ships in harbor in background. 15 x 11.5 cm. Identical to Items 16-19, in this folder, except this label has no letter bottom center.
    - Item 16: Empire State, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Excelsior. P. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering; image of two women in center, one holding anchor, one holding scales, with ships in harbor in background. 15 x 12.5 cm. Identical to Items 15 and 17-19, in this folder, except for the letter P in the center bo
    - Item 17: Empire State, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Excelsior. T. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering; image of two women in center, one holding anchor, one holding scales, with ships in harbor in background. 14.75 x 12 cm. Identical to Items 15-16 and 18-19, in this folder, except for the letter T in the cente
    - Item 18: Empire State, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Excelsior. W. S. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering; image of two women in center, one holding anchor, one holding scales, with ships in harbor in background. 14.75 x 12 cm. Identical to Items 15-17 and 19, in this folder, except for the letters W.S. in the c
    - Item 19: Empire State, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Excelsior. X. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering; image of two women in center, one holding anchor, one holding scales, with ships in harbor in background. 14.75 x 12 cm. Identical to Items 15-18, in this folder, except for the letter X in the center bottom.
    - Item 20: Enfield Mills., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      E M. Enfield, R.I.: W.H. Pope, ca. 1890s. Red and gold lettering against white background, within red, gold and black frame. 20.5 x 16.5 cm.
    - Item 21: English Cambrics Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      ____Yds. N.p., n.d. White lettering against gold background. 7.5 x 11 cm.
    - Item 22: English Satin Jeans Extra Fine, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      ___ Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against white background. 11.75 x 15 cm.
    - Item 23: English XXX Silesia, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against white background. 7 x 7 cm. Very similar to Item 24, in this folder, except for border.
    - Item 24: English XXX Silesia, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against white background. 6.75 x 7 cm. Very similar to Item 23, in this folder, except for border.
    - Item 25: English Soft Finish for City Trade, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and design on white background. 15.75 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 26: Enterprise Woolen Company, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Case ____ No. ____ Style ____ Yards ____. N.p., n.d. Black lettering on white background. 6.5 x 10 cm.
    - Item 27: Ermenegildo Zegna, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Milan, Italy: Ermenegildo Zegna, ca. 1910-1967. Company seal (still in use in 2010) centered against white background. 6 x 7.75 cm.
    - Item 28: Noir garanti inalterable (Black Guaranteed Unalterable), Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      E. Roussel. Roubiax, France: Emile Roussel, n.d. Gray lettering on very thin paper. 20.5 x 10 cm.
    - Item 29: Essex Mills manufactured expressly for city trade, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Picton, N.J.: American Felt Co., ca. 1900s. Black lettering against white/cream background. 20.5 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 30: Essex, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      ____Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against blue background, within red, gold and black border. 20.5 x 16.5 cm.
    - Item 31: Essex Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. Newburyport, Mass.: Essex Steam Mills, ca. 1844-1856. Black lettering within elaborate design with two eagles at top. 8.5 x 12.25 cm.
    - Item 32: Eureka Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering against white background, within gold border. 13.75 x 15.25 cm.
    - Item 33: Everett Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      No. Yds. Forbes Lith. 265 Wash. St. Boston. Lawrence, Mass.: Everett Mills, ca. 1862- 1868. Image of anchor leaning against crates with the initials E.M. on them, sailing ship and warehouses visible in background. 8 x 11.75 cm.
    - Item 34: Everett Classics: Made At The Everett Mills, Lawrence, Mass., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Photocopy. Sold by Smith, Hogg and Gardner. Lawrence, Mass.: Everett Mills, ca. 1922. Letters EC entwined in middle of label. Actual label attached to artifact 1965.32.10. 14 x 7.5 cm.
    - Item 35: Everett Steam Mills XX Flannels, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against yellow background. 25 x 20 cm.
    - Item 36: Excelsior, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      ____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Image of man holding flag with Excelsior on it. 8.5 x 13 cm.
    - Item 37: Excelsior Blue Cottons. Warranted Indigo Blue, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Warranted Indigo Blue. Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against yellow background. 25 x 20 cm.
    - Item 38: Excelsior Fine Cambrics. Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering within frame against white background. 12.25 x 15 cm. Identical to Items 39-41, in this folder, except for background color.
    - Item 39: Excelsior Fine Cambrics. Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering within frame against orange background. 12.25 x 15 cm. Identical to Items 38 and 40-41, in this folder, except for background color.
    - Item 40: Excelsior Fine Cambrics. Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering within frame against deep purple background. 12.25 x 15 cm. Identical to Items 38-39 and 41, in this folder, except for background color.
    - Item 41: Excelsior Fine Cambrics. Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering within frame against deep blue background. 12.5 x 15 cm. Identical to Items 38-40, in this folder, except for background color.
    - Item 42: Exeter Extra Fine Cambric, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Gold Medal Superior Finish. N.p., [1840-45]. Lithograph; B.W. Thayer & Cos. Lith. Boston. Gold lettering; gold shield surrounded by branches with image of angel and two women at top. 9.25 x 13.75 cm.
    - Item 43: Excelsior Pattern. Patented July 3, 1888., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Patented July 3, 1888. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against green background. 9.25 x 5 cm.
    - Item 44: Extra A. A. Nankins, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering against white background. 13.75 x 7.75 cm. Very similar to Item 45, in this folder; border and font slightly different.
    - Item 45: Extra A. A. Nankins, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering and border against white background. 13.5 x 7.75 cm. Very similar to Item 44, in this folder; border and font slightly different.
    - Item 46: Extra Heavy, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Dark blue lettering against light blue background; light copper colored border. 18.5 x 7.5 cm.
  - F, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: F F, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Red letters against dark red (striped) background within circular frame. 13 x 11 cm.
    - Item 2: Fabrique de Paris (Made in Paris), Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      ____Yds. N.p., n.d. Gray design, including crown at top against cream background. 9.5 x 13 cm.
    - Item 3: Superior Qualitie Fabrique de Paris (Superior Quality Made in Paris), Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and design against white background. 9.5 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 4: Fairy Lawns, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Wm. Lottimer & Co. Agents, New York. N.p., ca. 1800s. Image of a red rose on a yellow background. 7.75 x 10.75 cm.
    - Item 5: Fall River Soft Finish Extra Stout Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Fall River, Mass.?, n.d. Black lettering against yellow background with pastoral image in center. 19 x 22 cm.
    - Item 6: Fall River Superfine Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      No. Yds. Chas. H. Crosby, Pr., 3 Water St. Boston. Fall River, Mass.?, ca. 1857-1863. Dark gold lettering and frame against cream background. 12.5 x 16 cm.
    - Item 7: Falmouth Cheviot, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Round Thread. Pat. ____ ____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Red lettering within dark gold border against white background; image of swift at top. 15.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 8: Fancy Vestings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; black lettering within gold border against white background. 8 x 11 cm.
    - Item 9: Lustre mohair Serge Farr Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      No. ____ Quality ____ Yds. ____. Holyoke, Mass.: Farr Alpaca Company, n.d. White and black lettering against gold and white background; Doubleweight stamped across tag in red. 7 x 9.5 cm.
    - Item 10: Italian Cloth Farr Mills double warp., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Coffin, Altemus & Co. Sole Agents. No. ____ Yds. ____ Case ____. Holyoke, Mass.: Farr Alpaca Company, ca. 1889-1896. Gold lettering; heraldic shield in center. 9 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 11: Warranted Fast Color, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against white background. 9.5 x 3.5 cm.
    - Item 12: Warranted Fast Color, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      No.X191 12 Hfs. N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering, border and elephant in center against green background. 9.25 x 7.25 cm.
    - Item 13: Fast Colors, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Fountain in center, with Fast Colors written on banner draped around it. Orange background. 11.5 x 9.5 cm.
    - Item 14: Fearnaught Fancy Linings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      _____Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering within gold frame and border. 8.75 x 12 cm.
    - Item 15: Ferguson Superior Fine Twills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and herladic image in center, against deep blue background. 7.25 x 11.25 cm.
    - Item 16: Garner & Co. Fine 28 Inch B Cloths, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      These goods are full Madder and Warranted in all respects perfectly fast colors. The Cloths are uniform and equal in manufacture to any goods produced in this country. Garner & Co. [in script]. N.p., ca. 1800-1850. Black/white; large letter "B" in cen
    - Item 17: Fifth Avenue Foulards. Warranted 64 x 64, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      ____Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against orange background, within gold border. 11 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 18: Fisherville Extra Fine Bleached Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering within elaborate border; heraldic image at center. 15.5 x 20 cm.
    - Item 19: Fisherville Extra Fine Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Black lettering within elaborate frame; heraldic image at center. 20 x 25 cm.
    - Item 20: Fisherville Extra Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and elaborate frame against white background. 14.75 x 17.75 cm.
    - Item 21: Flower of the Mill Hundred Square, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Pink rose in center against black background. 20 x 24.5 cm.
    - Item 22: Foreign Manufacture Warranted Fast Colors, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      No.X282 12 Hfs. N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering, border and elephant in center against green background. 9.25 x 7.25 cm.
    - Item 23: Foreign Manufacture Warranted Fast Colors, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      No.X288A 12 Hfs. N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering, border and elephant in center against green background. 9.25 x 7.25 cm.
    - Item 24: Forest Mills., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Bridgeton, Me.: Forest Mills Co., n.d. Image of mill complex in country setting, set in blue and gold frame. 21.5 x 15.75 cm.
    - Item 25: Forthomme-Alleaume & Fils, Rouen Soieries Roberty (Roberty silks), Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Marque Deposee. Rouen, France: Forthomme-Alleaume & Fils, n.d. Gold lettering on very thin paper. 20.25 x 10 cm.
    - Item 26: Four leaf twill Qual.____Yds._____Case., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Qual. ____ ____ Yds. Case.____. Holyoke, Mass.: Farr Alpaca Company, n.d. Black lettering against white background, within gold and black border. 7.25 x 10 cm. (folded).
    - Item 27: Foxhall Worsteds, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Case ____ No ____ Style ____ Yds. ____. N.p., n.d. Image of jockey on horse in center. "Ticket Register, No 4033" stamped on reverse. 7 x 9.25 cm.
    - Item 28: Frankfort Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Yards. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against orange background. 20 x 24 cm.
    - Item 29: Frankford Print Works warranted can fast colours No.___Yds., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Frankford, Pa.: Frankford Print Works, no later than 1867. Image of two eagles flanking a shield (?) with a crown on top. 13 x 9 cm.
    - Item 30: Frankfort Superior Silesias, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against deep purple background. 11.25 x 8.25 cm.
    - Item 31: Franklin, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against red banner, within red and gold border. 24.25 x 19.25 cm.
    - Item 32: Franklin A Satteen Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Green lettering against white background, within elaborate gold, green and red frame. 15.75 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 33: Frankllin AAA Padding, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against yellow background. 14.25 x 17 cm.
    - Item 34: Franklin Extra Heavy Quality, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; red lettering against white background, within elaborate gold, white and blue frame. 8.5 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 35: Franklin Fancy Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Extra Width and Quality. N.p., n.d. Embossed; red lettering against white background, within elaborate gold frame. 9.5 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 36: Franklin Fine Silesias, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and portrait of Benjamin Franklin in center against dark green background. 7.5 x 9.75 cm.
    - Item 37: Franklin Mills satteen twills., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Franklin, N.H.: M.T. Stevens, n.d. Gold and red lettering against gold background within red, gold and white frame. 17.5 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 38: Franklin Satteen. Extra Quality, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Embossed; red lettering against white background, within blue and fold frame with doves. 9.25 x 12.25 cm.
    - Item 39: Franklin Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Extra Finish. No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Embossed; blue lettering against white background, within gold and green frame with doves. 9.25 x 12.25 cm.
    - Item 40: Franklin Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering against white background within green frame. 16.5 x 14.25 cm.
    - Item 41: Franklin Superior Cambric, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and frame against white background. 12 x 9 cm.
    - Item 42: Franklin Twilled Silesias. Superior London Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; red lettering within gold frame against white background. 9 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 43: French Figured Foulard, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Warranted Perfect and Fast Colors. No. _____ Yds. _____. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against white background. 8.25 x 10.75 cm.
    - Item 44: French River superior silesias satin finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      ____Yds. Mechanicsville, Conn.: French River Textile Co., ca. 1900-1920. Image of young country woman with lion in center; grey lettering. 8.5 x 13 cm.
    - Item 45: The Fruit Of The Loom: Non Such, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Providence, R. I.: B. B. & R. Knight, no earlier than 1875. Lithographed image of a pear. The Forbes Lith. M'F'G Co. Boston. 12.75 x 15.25 cm. The Fruit of the Loom name was adopted by Robert and Benjamin B. Knight in 1856 and was registered as a tra
    - Item 46: The Fruit Of The Loom: Ne Plus Ultra, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Providence, R. I.: B. B. & R. Knight, n.d. Lithographed image of a bunch of grapes. 12.5 x 15 cm. The Fruit of the Loom name was adopted by Robert and Benjamin B. Knight in 1856 and was registered as a trademark in 1871. The trademark has been owned b
    - Item 47: Fruit of the Loom [label], Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Providence, R. I.: B. B. & R. Knight, n.d. Registered by B.B. & R. Knight. Lithographed images of peach with grapes and raspberries. 23.5 x 18 cm. The Fruit of the Loom name was adopted by Robert and Benjamin B. Knight in 1856 and was registered as a
    - Item 48: Fruit of the Loom, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Providence, R. I.: B. B. & R. Knight, n.d. Lithographed image of a peach surrounded by grapes and raspberries. 22.5 x 17.5 cm. The Fruit of the Loom name was adopted by Robert and Benjamin B. Knight in 1856 and was registered as a trademark in 1871.
    - Item 49: Fruit of the Loom., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Providence, R. I.: B. B. & R. Knight, n.d. Lithographed image of a peach surrounded by grapes and raspberries. Copy 2. 21.5 x 16.75 cm. The Fruit of the Loom name was adopted by Robert and Benjamin B. Knight in 1856 and was registered as a trademark
    - Item 50: Fruit of the Loom, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Providence, R. I.: B. B. & R. Knight, n.d. Copyright secured by B.B. & R. Knight. Lithographed image of a group of plums and red and yellow cherries. 22.75 x 18 cm. The Fruit of the Loom name was adopted by Robert and Benjamin B. Knight in 1856 and w
    - Item 51: The Fruit Of The Loom: Imperial, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Providence, R. I.: B. B. & R. Knight, ca. 1870-1890. Lithographed image of a bunch of strawberries. Averell & Peckett, Lith. 20 & 22 Gold St., N.Y. 15 x 13 cm. The Fruit of the Loom name was adopted by Robert and Benjamin B. Knight in 1856 and was re
    - Item 52: The Fruit Of The Loom: Seek No Further, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Providence, R. I.: B. B. & R. Knight, n.d. Lithographed image of an apple. 13 x 15.5 cm. The Fruit of the Loom name was adopted by Robert and Benjamin B. Knight in 1856 and was registered as a trademark in 1871. The trademark has been owned by success
    - Item 53: The Fruit Of The Loom: Stump of the World, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Providence, R. I.: B. B. & R. Knight, n.d. Lithographed image of an orange/red peach surrounded by text. 12.5 x 15 cm. The Fruit of the Loom name was adopted by Robert and Benjamin B. Knight in 1856 and was registered as a trademark in 1871. The trade
  - G, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: G.D. Co. Fine Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Grosvenor-Dale Co.? N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering against green and white background; image of woman with anchor at sea in center. 12 x 15 cm.
    - Item 2: Garoga Woolen Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Case ____ Style ____ No. ____ Yds. ____. Ephratah, N.Y.? ca. 1800s. Arthur & Bonnell, N.Y. [printer]. Black lettering against white background; image of Native American in reeds on edge of water in center. 6.25 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 3: Gem Cottons, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      N.p., ca. 18900s. Image of woman in center wearing hat and undergarment (petticoat?), with a cross around her neck and a bracelet on each arm. Gold border. 23.5 x 30 cm.
    - Item 4: Gem Cottons, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      N.p., ca. 1890s. Image of woman in center leaning on support, wearing an undergarment (petticoat?) or negligee, with a cross around her neck and a bracelet on each arm. Gold border. 23.5 x 30 cm.
    - Item 5: Genoese Linen, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Trade Mark. N.p., n.d. Image of early sailing ship in center. 8.5 x 6.5 cm.
    - Item 6: Gilford Manu. & Mechanic Co. Warranted Indigo Blue, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      James Molineax, Agent. N.p., n.d. Image of eagle in center with banners above and below. 19.75 x 18 cm.
    - Item 7: Balmoral skirt Geo. H. Gilbert & Co., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      43 inches long 144 inches wide No.____ Double extra merino top. [Gilbertville, Mass.]: Geo. H. Gilbert & Co., ca. 1860s. Image of woman in full Balmoral skirt with green and white striped underskirt, wearing hat. 8 x 25.5 cm. (unfolded).
    - Item 8: Glasgow Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      South Hadley, Mass.? Glasgow Company? ca. 1860-1870. Black lettering against background of thistles. 11.5 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 9: Glencoe Extra Fine, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Lith. of C.H. Crosby, Boston. N.p., ca. 1857-1896. Gold lettering within elaborate frame against white background. 20 x 15.25 cm.
    - Item 10: Glen-Cove Full Madders, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Image of woman embroidering canvas in center. 10 x 15.25 cm.
    - Item 11: Glendale Company, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Image of woman in classical dress reading scroll in center, surrounded by gold, red and black frame. 19.5 x 25 cm.
    - Item 12: Glen Mills sheeting., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Forbes Co. Boston (lithographer). Oakdale, Mass.: Glen Mills, ca. 1900-1906. Image of stag on edge of lake with mountains in background. 25 x 20 cm.
    - Item 13: G. M. Richmond and Sons Madder Lilac Plates Warranted, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      ____ Yds. No. 23. Providence, R.I. before 1866. Gold lettering and gold frame against white background. 13 x 16 cm.
    - Item 14: Globe Steam Mills Newburyport, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Newburyport, Mass.: Globe Steam Mills, ca. 1867-1872. Lowell & Brett, Engrs., 228 Wash. St. Boston. Lavender printing against white/cream background; image of an arm holding a globe in center. 16 x 11 cm.
    - Item 15: Gloucester Company Prints, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Superior Madder Colours. N.p., n.d. Black/white, engraved; shows a woman with a feathered headress holding a sword and branch from the madder plant; she is surrounded by putti. 12 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 16: Gloucester Manfg Co. mourning prints David S. Brown & Co. No. ____, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Entered acc. to an Act of Congress by David S. Brown & Co. Philadelphia, Pa. in the office of the [label torn]. [Gloucester City, N.J.]: Gloucester Manufacturing Company, ca. 1865. Engraving; image of two women in classical dress mourning at a sacrcopha
    - Item 17: Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 3)